(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Matthew's parents went to the movies.
He was home alone.
He decided to eat all the junk food.
His parents usually yell at him when he
eats too much junk food.
They tell him it is not healthy to
eat too much junk food.
He was hungry.
He first opened the chips.
He had barbecue chips.
He opened some chocolate.
He had marshmallows.
He had some pizza.
He was starting to get full.
He decided to have some popsicle bars.
He ate a strawberry one.
Then he felt sick.
He knew now why his parents told him
not to eat too much.
His parents were coming home.
He heard the door unlocking.
He knew he was going to be in
trouble.